("One" by U2)
♪ Is it getting better ♪
♪ Or do you feel the same ♪
♪ Will it make it easier on you now ♪
♪ You got someone to blame ♪
♪ You say one love one life ♪
♪ When it's one need in the night ♪
♪ One love we get to share it ♪
♪ Leaves you baby if
you don't care for it ♪
♪ Did I disappoint you ♪
♪ Or leave a bad taste in your mouth ♪
♪ You act like you never had love ♪
♪ And you want me to go without ♪
♪ Well it's too late tonight ♪
♪ To drag the past out into the light ♪
♪ We're one but we're not the same ♪
♪ We get to carry each
other carry each other ♪
♪ One ♪
♪ Have you come here for forgiveness ♪
♪ Have you come to raise the dead ♪
♪ Have you come here to play Jesus ♪
♪ To the lepers in your head ♪
♪ Did I ask too much ♪
♪ More than a lot ♪
♪ You gave me nothin' now it's all I got ♪
♪ We're one but we're not the same ♪
♪ Well we hurt each other
then we do it again ♪
♪ You say love is a
temple love a higher law ♪
♪ Love is a temple love the higher law ♪
♪ You ask me to enter but
then you make me crawl ♪
♪ And I can't be holdin'
on to what you got ♪
♪ When all you got is hurt ♪
♪ One love one blood ♪
♪ One life you got to do what you should ♪
♪ One life with each other ♪
♪ Sisters brothers ♪
♪ One life but we're not the same ♪
♪ We get to carry each
other carry each other ♪
♪ One ♪
♪ Ooh ♪
♪ Baby baby baby ♪